ARMANDO ROSAS

Machine Rebuilder

Customer Service Representative

Automotive Technician

PROFILE

Ambitious, friendly and experienced professional seeking to find a career with a company that utilizes and values the contributions I consistently provide with both customers and team members. With over six years of customer service experience, I tested and implemented new techniques that reduced average customer wait times, improved work stations and increased work efficiency by up to 50%, while designing and implementing bench-testing procedures that decreased field repair times by up to 75%. I provided training to customers in person and over the phone on new equipment and procedures through effective communication and can resolve escalated customer service issues in both English and Spanish.

CONTACT

509-429-7176

seniorbuso@gmail.com

EXPERIENCE

Auto-Chlor Systems

2018-PRESENT

Rebuilds equipment to factory specifications
Uses a systematic approach to manage inventory of products
Uses a multi-line phone system to communicate with
customers and other team members
Oversees project management and dispatch field workers

Rodland Toyota

2013-2017

Performed maintenance and troubleshooting of vehicles Planned and organized day-to-day activities for shipping and receiving of vehicles and parts

Filed detail-oriented warranty, damage, and return claims in a fast-paced environment

Built relationships with customers to ensure satisfaction of repairs and improve success of company and increase sales

SKILLS

- Fluent in English & Spanish
- Self-motivated learner
- Detail-oriented
- Ability to work alone and as a team member
- Proficient in Windows 10/7 and Mac
 OSX and Microsoft Office Suite

Express Diving Services

2013-2017

Set up and maintained dive gear, including life support diving equipment and high pressure gas racks

Performed scheduled emergency checks on diving equipment to ensure safety of all customers and team

Responsible for detail-oriented approach of crane operations when divers are in the water and operations of hyperbaric decompression chambers

EDUCATION

Certifications

Front End Developer Program – in progress Responsive Web Design – in progress CSS, HTML, and PHP Certifications Skagit Valley College NATEF Certifications ADCI, DCBC, and NAUI Dive Certified

Upper Columbia Academy

High School Diploma